Safe Space is a horror, comedy film directed by Annabelle Attanasio.
A lonely young man uncovers a series of disturbing secrets when
he gets inducted into an all-male safe space.
Conor Pfister, played by Owen Campbell.
Sandy, played by David Rysdahl.
Kai, played by Ben Rosenfield.
Elvis, played by Alex Hurt.
Patch, played by Peter Vack.
Tal, played by Ariel Eliaz.
No Safe Spaces is a 2019 American documentary film directed by Justin Folk that features commentator Dennis Prager
and comedian Adam Carolla talking to college students and faculty about university safe spaces.
The documentary also covers free speech controversies occasioned when
conservatives are invited to speak in university settings.
The film was released in Arizona theaters on October 25, 2019, and was
successful enough to have a national release on December 6, 2019.
It has received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.